Freddy Roberts

CONTACT

E-mail: me@freddyroberts.com **Website:** www.freddyroberts.com

Phone: (615)-200-8245

SKILLS

HTML/CSS: Sass, Bourbon/Neat

 JAVASCRIPT: jQuery, Underscore.js, Backbone.js, React.js, and able to learn other MVC Frameworks

• **UX/UI:** Responsive Web Design

 Versioning/Collaborating: Git, GitHub & Strong foundation with working in team environments

Parse: Javascript SDK

Development Tools: CommandLine/Terminal, Bower, NPM, Gulp

ABOUT

I am pursuing a career in web development to engage my creative side, while also solving problems in a strategic way. Music and traveling are very strong passions of mine. While playing electric guitar for Hillsong Church, I had the opportunity to visit countries like England, Greece, Finland, Norway and Denmark. For the past 5 years I lived in Europe with my wife, who is Swedish. I love exploring different cultures, having lived on three continents has helped open my mind and given me a broader perspective on life.

EXPERIENCE

The IRON YARD Front-End Engineering - Nashville, TN 2015-2016 A program facilitating projects, requirements, and teaching skills to junior developers.

- 55+hours a week building web applications, using HTML, CSS, Javascript
- Project Planning, both individually & with a team
- Worked on cross-platform projects with Ruby on Rails server-side engineers.
- Final project, Drobe, a web app built with react.js using Parse as an infrastructure https://github.com/freddyroberts

DHL EXPRESS Courier - Stockholm, SE 2011-2015

- Excellence Time Management
- Route Planning
- Self Motivation

Hillsong Church Maintenance/Reception - Sydney, AU 2008-2010

- Team Work
- Service Focused Visitor Interactions

EDUCATION

Swedish A-D 2010 — 2011

SFI- Swedish for Immigrants

Stockholm, Sweden

Ministry & Leadership

2008 - 2009

Hillsong International Leadership College

Sydney, Australia

Freddy Roberts